<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on Brubaker&#39;s Soap Shack</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on Brubaker&#39;s Soap Shack</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All Rights Reserved [Brubaker&#39;s Soap Shack](/#/)</copyright>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/post-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who Are Are&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jason and Kimberly married in 2016 and settled in Crossville Tennessee.  It is a small town in Cumberland county Tennessee on the plateau.  In 2018 we opened our home and hearts to fostering children.  Since then 24 foster children have passed through our door.  Some stayed for only a few days, some months, some years, and some have found their forever home with us.  We were blessed to purchase our current home in 2019 and had enough space to take on our largest family yet bringing us to 12 kids, 6 ducks, and a tiny dog with big attitude.  We attend church regularly and are proud to call Pine Grove our church home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How we got started&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We began making soap as a school project with our oldest kiddo.  She enjoyed it and we did extra research and before ya know it we are all making soap and loving it&amp;hellip;.and let&amp;rsquo;s face it, with a family this big we go through lots of soap!  What had started as education, became a passion.  Then we got a call to take on a few more kiddos, and it became clear with this &amp;ldquo;yes&amp;rdquo; Kimberly would definitely be saying &amp;ldquo;no&amp;rdquo; to working outside of the home.  While out shopping for used dressers for the new kiddos, we stumbled across a booth with homemade soaps, many of the same scents as we were making, but the price was sky high, and the colors and shapes were not near as fun as what we were doing.  It hit us, that was the answer, if this person could do it with a decent bar of soap, surely we could do it with a great bar of soap!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
